Witch!
They've come to cause a scene!
Let's just call it off tonight.
Let's not bury Mengzhu just yet.
My lord
What's that noise?
It's... it's a Reanimated corpse!
A Reanimated corpse!
Mengzhu's a Reanimated corpse!
She's coming out!
How dare you!
Step back, all of you.
Isn't this Chief Mu's daughter, Mu Ying?
I haven't seen you in years.
You've grown even more beautiful.
Benefactor Li.
Chief Mu and I are very close...
...friends.
Don't mention him to me.
He's him, and I'm me.
This is feudal superstition!
Human sacrifice is against the law!
Inspector Mu.
What?
Master!
Master, I'm too late!
Stop crying.
Let's lift him out first.
Master!
He's not breathing.
Master, you can't die!
You haven't taken me to Drunken Sage Pavilion for roast chicken yet!
Master!
What are you doing?
Who hit me?
She did.
She-devil!
You hit way too hard!
Well, you aren't dead, are you?
You just fainted from lack of oxygen.
What do you mean, not dead?
She almost strangled me, you know!
Have you been reading too many storybooks?
This is acute cerebral hypoxia...
...causing hallucinations.
You were lying in that coffin for so long...
...with poor air circulation,
...leading to hypoxia,
...which disrupted your nerve signals.
And you claim Mengzhu tried to kill you?
She's already dead.
How could she kill you?
Master!
It...
It came back.
This...
This puppet has an Evil aura.
Every time someone dies in the Li mansion,
it appears.
No matter how far we throw it,
it's no use.
Madam...
First Madam, Second Madam...
after Third Madam died,
this little wooden puppet appeared beside their bodies.
I remember it with absolute certainty.
We destroyed this evil thing every time.
But...
it wouldn't take long
for this wooden puppet...
to just come back on its own.
This wooden puppet...
It has an Evil aura.
It can steal souls.
A broken wooden puppet stealing souls?
What a joke.
Where's the book?
Where did that book, Heavenly Craftsmanship, go?
Benefactor Li.
You're suspected of kidnapping and attempted murder.
Come back to the station with me.
I'm innocent, Inspector Mu!
I...
She...
It was all her doing!
I was only thinking of Master Li.
To quell the bloody disaster in the Li mansion,
we must let the dead fulfill their dying wishes.
Otherwise, the disasters in the Li mansion will never end!
I need to find a way to stay at the Li mansion,
to get Heavenly Craftsmanship back.
All right.
I'm not dead yet, am I?
I think...
we should investigate the cause of
Mengzhu's death first,
before talking about arresting anyone.
What?
You want to write Mengzhu's case into a storybook
and have your apprentice tell stories in restaurants?
My Master is highly learned.
And this She-devil...
is highly skilled in martial arts.
With the two of them joining forces,
they can definitely solve this case.
I heard Mengzhu say
your mansion has great food for guests.
Now I'll give you a chance to make up for your mistakes.
Maybe
my Master will forgive you.
Yes, yes, yes.
Chunmei!
Hurry and inform the kitchen
to prepare good wine and dishes!
Yes, Master.
Why does he look like a beggar?
All he does is eat all day.
Don't we have to eat before we work?
How did Mengzhu actually die?
Mengzhu died under mysterious circumstances.
We were in a hurry to bury her
because we're afraid that Mengzhu,
like those three concubines,
will become a Vengeful spirit
and haunt the mansion every night!
Since she died under mysterious circumstances,
I have to investigate it thoroughly.
Step aside.
I'll perform the autopsy.
I didn't know you could perform autopsies.
This is...
A needle mark on the victim's neck.
The head sustained a blow,
causing a skull fracture.
The fracture caused internal bleeding.
So,
Mengzhu's cause of death
was a skull fracture
and excessive blood loss.
This needle is highly suspicious.
A needle?
Where did it come from?
Master,
did someone break in
and kill her?
That's impossible.
The Li estate is guarded every night.
No outsider could possibly get in.
Who was Mengzhu with before she died?
Well...
Chunmei!
I'm here, Master!
Before Mengzhu died,
who else did she meet?
After dinner that day,
Miss heard two storytellers came to town,
so she took me to the restaurant.
We've met.
And we spoke with Miss Mengzhu.
But what about later?
Miss was upset that you ignored her,
so she took me to the temple fair.
She bought a whole bunch of things.
Take a look, miss.
It's so pretty.
It's beautiful.
This umbrella is lovely.
Right?
How much is this?
Miss! Miss!
Come take a look!
Then we headed back after dark.
Late that night,
stray cats kept Mengzhu awake,
so she insisted on swapping rooms with me.
I never expected that the next morning,
I'd find Mengzhu already dead.
What about this needle?
Where did it go?
What needle?
I didn't see any needle.
Mengzhu was clearly murdered!
Why didn't you call the police,
instead of tying him up for a ghost marriage?
When the previous three wives died,
we did report it to the police.
But the police found nothing at all.
If we had to rely on you police,
we'd be better off on our own.
I...
Master Li,
could you please
take us to Mengzhu's room
to have another look?
Early that morning,
when my daughter was found,
her body was lying right here.
What exactly happened?
Did you see the killer?
After Mengzhu was hit by the needle,
she fell off the bed.
She hit her head on this cabinet,
which caused the skull fracture.
There's no murder weapon in the room,
and the killer left no traces.
Where did the needle come from?
Why is there an extra table here?
It wasn't here before.
This Zhong Kui wood carving...
my daughter bought it specifically for me to ward off evil.
The wooden puppet is wet.
There's a small hole in the roof.
There really is a small hole.
Bookworm,
how did you know?
The Li residence has always been well-maintained.
How could there be a hole?
This wooden puppet...
was rigged with a hidden weapon.
It rained heavily the night of the incident.
Someone removed the roof tiles,
creating a puddle.
I don't care. I'm switching rooms with you.
Dad!
Alright, alright.
Fine.
Oh, you.
A hole was chiseled in the roof,
so the water leaked through,
dripping right onto the wooden puppet.
The rainwater triggered the hidden weapon in the puppet.
The weapon fired a silver needle.
Mengzhu was struck by the silver needle,
crashed into the cabinet,
and died from a skull fracture.
So,
the accumulated water
was what really caused the puppet to kill.
Using rainwater and a puppet
to commit a locked-room murder.
Exactly.
Then what's the motive?
Right.
Mengzhu was a wealthy young lady.
Why would anyone kill her?
This room
was originally Master Li's bedroom.
Mengzhu swapped rooms with Master Li.
Therefore,
the killer's real target
must have been Master Li.
Someone is trying to kill me.